I want to examine one of my understanding
is that today, still,
if a firm wants to manage the user or
roles, still they rely on SAA team.
It's not fully self-serve.
Yeah, correct. OK.
Is the auto auto provisioning across
systems is not there yet. OK.
It has not been built.
Even with UAM,
the point is we provide a tool for them
to request access,
but then the execution part will be
remain with as a one.
capacity, budget, timing, need,
dependencies, the road mapping issue.
I mean, I mean, no, no, no.
I mean the responsibility that why it
cannot be full self-serve,
the provisioning. What is missing?
There's no integration. Oh,
because of the lack of the integration.
Okay, let's go further.
And to get that done is just simply the
prioritization problem.
It's not a solution problem,
it's a prioritization problem.
As you can see,
we're six weeks into the end of the
quarter.
We're still trying to cut corners on the
MVP.
So that's how these things come about.
We'll dive into the roadmap next week.
Graham knows it all too well. All right,
so we'll cover packages today because to
implement the ability for somebody to get
a feature,
Compass does it in a little bit of a
funny way.
It's non-standard,
and that's because we tried to bastardize
a standard model,
the standard RBAC models to to fit our
needs. And this is where Candi,
maybe you need to help me explain it,
because I don't even I don't even think I
don't I don't know if we documented this
rip the.
Rip the band-aid. Okay,
so we'll get back into this later.
We're going to focus on the feature
packaging today.
I tried to write down some concept.
These are actually just notes for me,
so I remember to say it.
So we're going to talk about the feature
management flow and then how that gets
into how we package and assign features,
because this is a key platform concept.
So
Recall,
remember we talked about Firm 360 and we
talked about Compass and we talked about
the relationship between the two, right?
We talked about firm configuration being
the source of truth for what a firm
should have. That's right.
And then based on that,
we would take the firm subscriptions are
defined.
and we would implement it on the platform.
So when we talk about feature management
in this context,
we're talking about features that exist
in Compass,
not all the features that might be
available in our ecosystem.
Because Compass can only manage what
Compass can manage, right?
So I want to first of all make that
distinction.
Not every subscription goes into here.
A good example is, and again,
typically is contingent on prioritization.
So we've always wanted Compass to be
single entry point to all of your digital
services. Well,
it is not that today because we haven't
done integrations with a bunch of stuff.
It's just sitting in the back walk
somewhere. And so.
you can't manage it in Compass, right?
Which means when we talk about passing
over the firm subscription on what they
have access to,
there are some things that doesn't make
sense to pass over, right?
So we retain Firm 360 as the master
catalog and the master kind of definition
of what a firm has,
and then we implement the Compass portion
of it in Compass.
Okay, okay.
So it means that based on last meeting,
it means that, for example,
there are a couple of services,
for example, in SC,
that has not been integrated with the
contest in terms of authorization or
authentication, whatever.
That's why still we cannot fully manage
them and say, okay,
when they onboard the catalog inside data
from 360 to Compass,
maybe it's not a portion of them still do
not exist because of that lack of
integration. Yeah,
because we only want to onboard them.
Like first principle matters here, right?
The role of Compass is to implement the
configuration for that flow.
And you can only implement what's there.
You can't implement what's not there.
Exactly.
So I can't implement Creases because
Creases is not a thing.
Creases is a portfolio management system
that our firms use today and they buy it
off us.
Yeah,
but it's a completely different system.
It's right, like third party. Yeah,
that's right. It's a third party.
It's an add-on. It's not in the ecosystem.
We have a contract with that third party.
We issue user IDs through increases,
user admin is increases,
everything's increases, right?
So our firms can still buy from us.
So on Firm 360, we're going to say.
this firm has increases,
so we're gonna bill them, right?
And then we even get a report increases
to reconcile number of users because we
bill per user.
But that's directly increases,
that's not encompassed.
Okay, but what I understand is,
and it's a good integration to be honest,
but I want to know that what extra you
expect to have to say, okay,
Persis is under my full control because
You already are navigating the user.
It's authorization.
We're not doing any of that. Oh.
It's like I said,
you want creases tomorrow, your firm A,
you want creases.
Here's a user ID to creases.
But coming from compass. Nope.
Here's a user ID to creases.
I'm not giving you a compass ID.
I'm giving you a creases ID. Oh, sorry.
I thought that it is a CX ID. OK.
Yes, crazy.
Maybe I should have said digit or some
other thing that doesn't start with a C.
Yeah, no, no,
so it's there are things that you get
direct login for,
even our research solutions.
So you'll hear us talk about Evercore.
I'm going to give you an Evercore ID to
log in. Okay, I understand that.
Sometimes business has some priority, say,
okay,
I want this research to be available to
all my partners. I don't care,
you need to be, that's right, exactly,
that's, but it's one thing.
The other thing is that if we had,
or if we are planning to have...
a kind of framework for third party tools
to say, okay,
this is I understand your priorities,
but this is something that we can do more
standard. So this is my framework.
You can tell to third party,
you can integrate with some very simple
API communications.
And then now I'm ready to broadcast it to
all the
Okay. Yeah,
that's we'll talk about that's our
platform integrations playbook.
I'm hoping we can actually get into that
today if you have time. Yes,
that's but remember the decision is not
that straightforward.
It might be always right like so we want
the integration, like you said,
the integration framework to be available
always because part of the platform is
remember non-core.
We're here to facilitate the integration,
so why wouldn't we have a standardized
set of, I guess,
integration points that you need to talk
to, and we're not changing it.
The third party has to consume it, right?
That always has to be available,
but we might not decide to use it all the
time. That is.
a business decision. More often than not,
it comes down to, okay,
what's everybody working on and is it
worth it, right?
Is there a lot of value in us doing that?
Or can I get away with giving out a
separate ID and not having that
centralized view encompass of this
particular firm that has users over there
on the other side?
We get away with that actually quite a
lot,
and especially if it's emerging products,
right?
So maybe I only have one or two firms
piloting it.
We're not doing the integration because,
you know what,
I don't know how many of these licenses
I'm going to sell.
So why would I put money into it?
Because usually integration costs
something, right? Yeah.
So those are more kind of business level
decisions that would be taken.
to say,
do we want to pursue and what degree of
integration do we want to pursue?
Because you can do a very simple one,
right,
which is just an identity integration,
or you can go to town and shove it into
Compass.
There's incremental costs of doing that.
And then there's a...
incremental kind of strategic decision to
do that work, right? They go hand in hand.
So even though, you know,
it might make sense,
we said compass is a single pane of glass,
right? It's the single entry point.
Why don't we do it? Well,
sometimes those decisions take place
because we're not sure where to place
that product. Thanks. Okay.
Or the vendor might say,
I'm going to charge you like 1,000,
000 bucks. Then we're going to be like,
well, that's not worth it. Then we go, oh,
I don't know if you're a partner or not,
but there's a whole separate,
we'll get into that business integration.
Yeah. Yeah, I understand. Yeah.
So how do you, then how do you implement?
So let's go back to how do you then
implement that configuration? Well,
first of all, that feature has to exist,
right? Yeah.
And then we have to give it to the firm,
and then the firm has to give it to the
user. Okay, three steps.
The way we do that is,
you've seen some of it already, Ali.
I don't know how deep you kind of took a
look at behind the scenes,
but the first step really is to be able
to register the feature. Right. Today,
how we do that,
so should we do current Candi or should
we do Q4?
Two for.
OK, well, we used to, well, actually,
you still have to describe it. No,
let's do, let's do today,
and then we build, yeah, on top. We,
we actually look at the user, yesterday.
OK, good, good. So, she, yeah,
he got some some information or some
explanation from Maisha. OK, good. Not to.
Not to sidetrack this,
I don't want to do it here,
but would I be likely using the historic
or the Q4? The Q4. Okay.
So a sidetrack is very relevant. Okay.
Doesn't change anything,
it's still a little bit ****** **.
So a little bit? A little bit,
a little bit.
Something that we are doing today,
but not it's after post-feature
registration.
I don't know where the feature
registration takes place, but no, okay,
let's get into it. So,
the way the way we assign features to
firms and users is.
We never started with the concept of
feature management at the beginning.
We talked about that, right,
five years ago. We, well,
we started with the idea,
but nobody did anything with it.
What we did instead was to say, well,
we need to represent features somehow,
right? So we decided, well,
we didn't decide, architecture decided,
we're going to represent features as
resources.
And these resources,
I don't even know what they are.
There's things like entry points to the
feature itself. And I don't know if,
Candi,
you want to get into like the different
types of resources we have available and
why they exist.
Do you want to explain the...
By each concept, yeah,
the resource like definition of a
resource, so that we can talk, yeah,
so I think the we move from roll back,
R back into this kind of a resource
management concept is we're breaking down.
It doesn't matter which row,
but we're breaking down,
kind of trying to manage the features.
But features,
we don't actually have a definition of
features.
And how we see it is because you want to
show something on the platform,
so you have a navigation.
You have to show it on the left nav.
And so we call that a module.
So I have to present the module is
clickable,
and then you go to the orders page,
you go to the accounts page. So we will,
we have one type as module. And then,
but then when you go to the orders page,
there's a lot of things you can do.
You can view the order list.
You can submit an order,
you can upload a file for the mutual fund
basket. So the different things, we,
again,
we didn't have the concept of feature,
but we call it different resources. So,
and is required by the endpoint.
If you want to click on the create other
button, so maybe that's one endpoint,
control that button.
and it will be controlled on the UI,
it will be controlled by a resource.
So you have one resource saying create
order, and that resource will be allowed,
will be assigned to some user,
but not all users. And that user,
if they have to create order resource,
then the screen will show the create
order button. And so you can click on it.
And then when you click on it,
the endpoint would check,
do you have to create all the button,
create all the results? If you do,
then it's a legit call.
So that's how the permission management
was done or the authorization is done in
that way.
So we kind of separate, you know,
here from the UI is one thing,
whether or not you see something.
So that's why we keep saying resource is
something to control your UI visibility,
whether you see it or not.
But then at the end,
it would be something the resource is
also.
Something the endpoint or the back end
has to control, has to read it. So,
if in the past, like,
way back when we first implement that,
something could see the button,
but then it it doesn't matter,
the endpoint doesn't check the results,
so that's a big gap. Like,
you can see the button when you click on
it, it doesn't matter, maybe someone just.
..
got break break into the system and were
able to submit the endpoint and then
because the endpoint doesn't check the
resource correctly.
So that's the gap at that time.
So now we kind of tied up the UI
visibility and the back end validation.
So
In the TECH terms,
they are implementing some common library,
so the UI will be using all the common
library would would define the UI with
stability or define the resource types,
and then the back end would use the same
or make sure that the back end common
library and...
what the front end using are consistent.
So then what I expect to be controlled on
the UI would be controlled at the back
end.
And it's also important the back end
would check the same resource because we,
as we mentioned,
we're opening up for the API marketplace.
Someone could bypass this UI and call our
endpoint directly,
so that's why we have to synchronize or
make sure that the front end and the back
end are checking the same thing. Yeah,
it it wasn't that way in in the when we
first started the chat boxes.
for people to choose what module they
want to see.
But this is now the case. Any question?
Uh, is it all confusing, or no, no, I,
yes?
For me,
I think if I want to map it visually,
for example, here I am in accounts. So.
Let's say that, let me open up my...
Do you have a JSON, Candi,
of a resource definition?
So we can see it with our eyeballs.
Open the JSON file. Yeah, I can actually,
can I share my thing?
I can actually show it on the UI, yeah.
First.
At least doing that anyway. Yeah,
I tried to because we do it,
I'm doing it time to time.
It's one of the...
Do you want to drive or do you want me to
show my screen?
I can share my screen and ask questions,
whatever you wish.
Let me share my screen so I'll go to the
right place and then you can ask
questions.
Was it up here?
I'm showing, I'm showing, yeah, OK, so...
Yeah, so on this side,
these are all modules. Yeah. Yeah.
And modules would link to basically open
up the page where you would land on.
But then...
Mm.
Let me go to find a profile and then show
you the packages.
Question? Oh, yep. Not yet. Not good.
I want to make sure, Candi, can we, yeah,
can we do,
make sure we understand what a resource
is?
We don't want to get into packages yet.
Resource, OK.
Like this one's a control bank,
but I can bring up the profile to show.
What do we mean about that?
Is there a good place here?
We show it here. I don't,
we don't wanna get it. I don't know what,
let's see it. I don't know what,
let's see it, yeah. So, for example...
So, forget about these are packages,
but we,
we're not looking at the packages yet,
but in here, depends on the anyway,
depends on the user package you chose,
and the resources of the module below
would be different.
And modules are something, as I said,
it drives what you can see on the nav
when you log into the page.
So without going in too much details,
each one of these ones will link to
something on the left that would drive
the UI visibility,
whether or not you can go inside.
to use the features.
And, but the tricky thing is,
these ones are modules,
but behind the scene,
every module would also link to some
resources. So, for example, I have Katie,
I think it's easier if you pull up the
JSON template, the JSON template,
the package template. This is too...
This is another layer above it.
That's too. Can I show it in here? Yeah,
as long as as long as we can see the
package definition. Package definition is,
let me think.
Mmh.
I don't, I don't,
I don't see how you would show it in.
Yeah, it's showing here. Yeah,
it's a center showing here template data.
Do you know what template do you have?
What is that?
I can ask for Owen spreadsheet if it is
easier.
Okay.
Yeah, we downloaded from here, so...
Just, I don't remember which. Yeah, here.
Is it okay?
No,
I want to go into an admin all package
template definition where it shows all
the resource list of that package.
You want to look at Jason? Yeah.
I hope to do something.
You want which one? Manage all?
Doesn't matter. There you go.
I'm not sure that one.
There's enough of the whole one.
close enough. close enough.
This is weird though. It's just GI.
So this is some Jessie. Yeah.
This is the package template ID and the
name and the description, yeah? We don't,
not, not, we're not there yet.
Well,
I want to show you what's inside of it.
Yeah.
close enough is a fun package,
close enough, yeah, close enough.
Hmm.
Okay, so we don't wanna,
we don't wanna take a little,
we don't care for the assignments for now.
Let's bypass that.
There we go. This is all the time. Yeah.
What is the?
Make sure you can download.
Thursday.
ET.
Online security services.
SIS Security Industry Services has an
online security services system.
I know what it is.
Where did you get that little number?
I have. Okay, this is going to take two.
We can just talk about it conceptually.
Mhm.
Conceptual.
I don't want to sink time into this if we
can't find one. I can find one.
I think Tash has the JSON files.
If you want to think of that.
Let's do conceptual and then maybe we
reinforce with eyeballs once you get a
hold of it or once Owen shares the
spreadsheet. Okay.
So, because I want to go into, okay,
let's do this. Let's, okay,
come back to what's that plan.
Can talk to me? Yeah, no, no, I can do it.
Okay. Well,
I can summarize what you just said,
because I'm trying to write it down in
here as well,
because I'm terrible at documentation. So,
no, you're fast. I don't think you were.
I'm not sharing anymore.
Should I ask for a juice offer? Yes, OK.
Okay, we're back. I'm just writing.
There's no visuals.
We'll do the visuals later.
I thought I had a visual,
but it didn't work. Okay. So conceptually,
resources are things.
I don't even know what they are,
but they're things. Like,
are they endpoints? Are they like,
I don't know. That's why I want to see it.
But there's basically definitions that
represent a feature. And to Candi's point,
there's different like types of resources
that belong to a feature.
We don't need to worry too much about it.
It's more of like a technical engineering
detail.
But just know that like there's specific
types of resources that we care about.
For instance,
Candi said there's a module resource or
UI resource.
We define that as part of the feature to
say that thing has a UI and it has an
entry point.
So we got to make that available. Then,
but these resources aren't built into the
app.
It's actually a mapping to what's
actually within the app. So for Graham,
this is just awareness for you.
You don't need to know that these things
exist.
You just need to know that we're going to
take the app and we're going to map it to
resources.
Right.
There are entitlement resources that
actually control specific actions.
So we define that.
And depending on how we characterize the
resources,
it could be used for different things.
Like do we show or hide it in the UI?
Do we let people check or uncheck it?
That's also part of the resource
definition.
So if you look at the full list of all
the resources within the feature,
you should kind of know what's
controllable.
in that feature, right?
So we'll take a look at it with the JSON
later.
But that's a really important concept
because that's our only representation of
a feature in Compass.
So we gotta make sure, like,
our dev teams do make sure they
understand all the resources that make up
a feature,
and any where we need to assign somebody
to that feature,
we actually need to assign those.
resources to the person. Yeah, not,
we're not assigning features,
we have to assign those resources.
So it's the way,
because we kind of went bottom up, right?
And then we never abstracted that detail
when we built this thing.
We didn't have the feature management
concept.
What we're going to introduce is with
feature management is we're going to put
a name to that collection of resources.
Okay, so you're putting that in place.
Putting that in place. That's right.
Yeah, yeah, like Q4. Well, sort of,
but not really, but...
kind of get into it because and you'll
see why in a minute. So, right,
so features are a collection of resources.
People only get access to features if
they actually have those resources on
their profile.
And the way we kind of group all of this
stuff together, as you can see,
it can get really cumbersome when you
have 100 and...
20 features and each feature has at least
like what two to five candies resources
that defines that feature.
Talk about like.
a resource list, that's massive.
And so when we said, okay,
how do you apply this to a firm and how
do you apply this to a user? Well,
first of all,
a user can't be assigned something that a
firm doesn't have, right? Remember,
firms have subscriptions and they might
not subscribe to everything.
And if they don't subscribe to everything,
the user within that firm can't get
everything. They shouldn't even,
like we shouldn't even allow them to be
assigned to it, right?
So our first step is actually to
introduce this concept of a firm package.
And a package is really just a list of
resources, right?
And so when we say we want to assign
something to a user,
we first have to assign that feature to a
firm.
And therefore,
a firm needs to have a package that has
that list of resources in it.
We then went kind of further to say, well,
we don't want to define 400 firm packages
for 400 firms,
because that's a lot of packages, right?
And then every time we update or onboard
a new feature,
we have to actually go and update.
and add those resources to 400 packages.
So we said, let's simplify a little bit.
Let's see where the common,
lowest common denominator.
It's very tactical. This,
we don't have to stick to this if we
don't want to.
Let's find the lowest common denominator
so that we can say, you know what,
maybe all IDs have the same feature set.
And then maybe all PMs have the same
feature set.
and it's just slightly different.
So we created an IB front package and a
PM front package.
So the PM package, if you recall, PMs,
we own the accounts,
they don't have control functions.
You won't see those features in that PM
package.
You'll see the approval functions, right,
in the IP package.
That's the first distinction.
Right, okay, so a firm needs a package,
otherwise we don't know what features
they have.
We can't say this firm has this set of
features that you subscribe to.
Right,
and then when you look into the firm
package,
it's still a list of all those resources,
yeah,
that they that they're eligible for gets
associated with that firm.
Okay, it's no different to like, I mean,
resource is just another fancy word for
like, like a feature package, right? Yeah.
Okay. However,
this is where it gets really fun,
is we also said that, okay,
if I assign a package to a firm,
I also then need to assign whatever's in
there to a user.
So we said, well, how do we do that?
This thing needs to be tied to
permissions, right?
It's not just a feature configuration at
the firm level,
because that that doesn't control
permission. This is just like I need to,
like I need to define like the package
for that firm, right?
So there's no access controls associated
with it. But when it comes to a user,
I do need to restrict.
what a user should have access to based
on what we assigned to that user profile.
Now,
because our user controls and user access
is actually hosted in Okta.
Right, that's our solution.
That's our IAM solution for our users.
Opta is not really compatible with
feature management.
Okta is more compatible with RBAC,
which is role-based access control.
So in order for me to provision a user in
Okta, I need to give it a role.
And that role definition has to contain
something.
And I can only give the user one role,
not multiple roles. Well, as of.
1.
0 and then we'll talk about how we not do
that because that's not an actual
realistic limitation or architect at the
time just decided that he was going to
not do that. So.
It's a very important limitation.
So if I only have one profile per user in
Okta,
then I need to figure out how to define a
package for a user without defining 9000
packages,
because we have 9000 users on the
platform. Yeah. So what we did,
and this is our...
the meat of the discussion today,
actually I'm going to update this,
is when it comes to user role assignment,
we decide to say, okay,
we will still use the package concept
because again,
you have to have resources to get access
to the platform, right?
So I do need to create a package for a
user on top of the.
package for the firm.
I can't just say the package for the firm
because that's defined in compass,
the compass concept, right?
It doesn't go into Octa,
Octa doesn't communicate with it.
I need to be able to kind of still assign
resources and have that saved in the user
profile.
So we said a user package is actually a
role.
Okay.
So then now I can have a user package.
That has a specific set of resources in
it,
and that's what Okta recognizes as the
role. This is very abstracted.
Candi can actually tell you, like,
or JP can tell you the actual, like,
I'm probably oversimplifying this, and so,
as long as I assign a user with the user
package, that basically is signing.
Hello.
Remember,
we don't have fixed roles in firms.
Firms don't operate.
So then what we decided to do was, well,
I need to overcome this one-for-one
limitation where I can only assign a user
with one user package.
So I'm going to predefine all the core
combinations that a user can have.
OK, so if.
So that at least there is a at least at
least a user package combination that if
I go back to here.
Right.
This why I did this page.
If I have an advisor transition team that
only wants to do account management and
transfers, but manage, manage.
I have another group here that does very
similar things,
but they want to do approvals.
At least those are those are now two
different definitions, right?
Like they're two different packages.
I have to create two different packages
for them. Those are two different roles.
Yeah, right.
So I have to have a combination that
allows me to grant this group access to
just manage and this group access to just
control. Okay.
Makes sense. Right. The worst part is,
okay, that's just one set of capabilities,
right? That's just account management.
What if I want somebody to be able to
manage accounts and trade? Well,
now I need a role for that.
What if I want somebody to manage orders,
but then approve servicing?
Now I need a different role for that.
And you can see how the combinations
start to explode.
Right, but at the end, it's not 9000,
it's 50 at that point. So,
for for what we did for user packages is
we actually went down this path of
defining all the eligible combinations of
features that people can get.
And we settled on a fixed list of
standardized packages,
which is actually what you see in the
user admin console, right?
And so when you look at this...
Ohh, ****, I got the wrong one,
or is this my global admin?
No, it's not. Hold on.
And it's Penny Lam 2.
Explain the two logins later.
So when you see her in the access control,
these roles, you see these combinations,
admin all, admin orders,
admin service request, manage service,
manage accounts and profiles, manage all,
manage orders only,
manage service requests only,
manage transactions with servicing plus
orders, view only,
which is view everything, right?
Like you see that these are now starting
to look like okay.
There are different combinations of both
the capability, right, the core, yeah,
accounts, servicing orders, trades,
combinations of that,
and combinations of view, manage, control,
approve,
and this is how you give users a role,
yeah, right, which is the user package,
which is a...
a predefined set of features that allow
you to manage orders and trades. Okay.
Right.
That's how you give it to them.
So the unfortunate part about this is
like,
ideally we wouldn't have gone down this
path because when we first started on
this,
we said there's four core services at
minimum. There's also add-ons.
And so we need to be able to actually
independently assign features and feature
access to.
Affirm,
and we need to have a like a like a
composable version of the role.
So technically, if Optic goes by RBAC,
it's only it only supports RBAC and it
only supports role definitions,
and we need to give a user multiple roles,
right?
So you can be administering something,
controlling something, managing something,
I don't care. So that's...
one point, when you hear us talk about 1.
5, it's a solvable problem.
We need to switch it to that model at
that point,
otherwise it's still going to get very
complicated.
Graham, you are frowning.
Soak in it in. That's okay.
So to show you what that looks like,
I hope it's here, Andy. I found it.
You found it? Yeah. Okay,
I'll do the table and then,
so you will now,
don't worry about this part.
So when it comes to user packages,
remember user packages,
group of resources,
we decided then to create.
These all these combinations.
just so that they fit into the role.
So there's about 26 right now, I think,
that the numbers are all messed up.
And then each package,
like a manage orders here, is defined,
like I said, by which core capability.
So account, this is account management,
account servicing, orders, and trades.
Don't worry about,
I don't know why I did this.
Gotta get rid of that grouping.
It's defined by, okay,
what capabilities is in here.
So if it's orders, I'm gonna give,
I'm gonna put all the resources that's
related to managing orders into this
package. And then this package,
because we need to also control, okay,
is it the view manage controller access
features that this has? Okay,
this is a manage orders profile,
so I'm only gonna package the view manage.
resources into it as well.
It's this plus this that creates that
package definition.
In contrast to maybe we look at kind of
manage orders and trades, you'll see that,
okay, it's not just orders,
it's trade as well,
and I need to see that it's view and
manage.
I'm gonna find all the resources and all
the features that are related to orders
and trades.
And remember, within those resources,
there are entitlement resources versus UI
resources.
So the team will know if we tell them
this, they're going to register, like say,
the orders module as a UI resource.
They're going to register and manage
equity, mutual funds,
and options as resources.
They're going to know that if I see
anything that's in control, because the...
you know,
a module might have a control feature,
right?
I'm not going to put that in this package.
And that's how we track what features are
in what packages.
Crazy, and if you explode this,
because you can't really see it right now,
because you gotta know,
is the different packages are really just
different variations of this. So,
here under column three,
manage account and profiles,
the access features.
is trading orders and trades or manage
accounts and profile? Yes. The ones.
It's okay. What features?
It's open and modify. Yeah, that's it.
Open and modify accounts. That's it.
Only that. Yeah. And then.
It can view and manage, not control,
not process. So far, it's fine.
The thing is that the typical team,
when they receive this indicator from UI,
they have a mapping on the back end.
that maps through JSON whatever to the
resources, the list of resources,
registered resources.
Who provides that mapping?
That's what I want to understand it.
Who is engineering that mapping is coming
from us, coming from SA team or? No,
it's a collaboration. Oh, okay.
So product team defines the feature and
what controls we need to have in that
feature or in the module in case we're
building a module.
We kind of say this module has certain
things it needs to do.
IT team to find the resources for the app.
And then IT team talk to platform team
based on this list of resources.
We will give them a feature onboarding
plan that says high level definition,
this is the feature,
and then get the list of resources from
the app team.
Resources gotten. Okay,
now that platform onboarding team is
going to figure out what do I do with
this set of resources and they specialize
in knowing, like it's Paul basically,
right? They specialize in knowing, okay,
based on this group of resources,
I need to put a UI resource here so that
the navigation works.
I need to put the UI and the entitlement
resources in the packages.
I'm going to do that based on what
product team tells me.
which packages I need to add it to, right,
based on this.
And that's how they get onboarded.
Okay, I understand.
It's all like manual by the way. Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
I can now I can connect the dots,
but why it is fragmented? I mean,
why it is not consistent? I mean...
It's not very hard to provide a
relationship between features, resources,
and so forth.
We just started Bottom Up five years ago.
You're the first one said that it's not
so hard to do. It's very hard to do. No,
no, because that...
The whole platform only recognizes
resources.
So to move to the level of features,
you need to refactor the whole platform.
Sorry, maybe I explained badly,
because right now this mapping is taking
place.
by R&D team, engineering team. Yeah,
it's already doing that. Yeah,
we have tons of like spreadsheets about
this. Yeah, for sure. We even have one,
like, you know,
that's about the feature registry. Yeah,
I think the challenge is, as Play said,
the resources, whatever mapping,
control the entitlement,
as well as the UI.
presentation.
So a lot of time is because the
limitation on the platform UI,
it has to show things very specific way.
So then you need to kind of create a
grouping of the resources in a very
specific way.
Otherwise you cannot render something
this way.
So if the results only control or the
JSON package only control the entitlement
part, it's easy. It's like one-to-one.
But then you also have to cater how you,
because the navigation is not just
falling.
So something like GIC should be under
orders and then trade allocation should
under something.
So that hierarchy build up.
would require you to group the resources
differently.
And then by grouping the resources,
you also have to cater for someone.
Maybe I need access to GIC,
but I don't have trading capability.
But the trading is the parent navigation.
So you have to show the orders.
But then when the people go in,
you don't want to show show them like the
create order or view order capability.
So you we're mixing the UI control and
the entitlement control at the same time.
So the that's why.
pause very valuable because he know how
to navigate all of these.
Even I don't understand,
sometimes they have to group things very,
very weirdly, very differently. So that's,
I think that's the challenge. Well,
in terms of how the resource get used and
because of that,
when you go then to replace this, right,
because again,
like when you load the platform.
What does the code do?
It looks for what's in, like,
it looks for user context.
It looks for what do you have. Okay,
if you have this,
then I show a certain number of UI
resources grouped in a certain way, right?
Because I don't want to show you what you
don't have. That,
even that loading is based on resources.
Like everything in the platform is based
on resources.
So yes, we have the mapping,
but because we didn't have a data model
that has the feature to resources like
mapping stored like systematically to
undo all of that, to redo it,
you're thinking like it's probably one,
like at least 1/4 for you to undo that
and redo that. It's not impossible,
but it'll take a long time and it will be
a full regression for everybody.
and all the app on the platform,
because all the apps are set up this way
as well.
So that's our issue is it's at some point,
we're going to want to clean it up,
because we really want to define things
based on features, not resources.
It's messy. But until then,
somebody just needs to keep track of, oh,
this set of resources actually mean this
feature.
But it kind of like it kind of works now,
but Paul is keeping track of it,
if that is.
Explicitly a like the intent to verify,
are we tracking, you know,
order of magnitude of debt we're taking
on?
Do that? We know, yeah, well,
and I don't think it's tracking.
It plays out every time we onboard
feature, right? Yeah, like today.
So,
and then if you think about the severity
from a prioritization perspective,
I think at first there were a lot of
issues.
because nobody had the expertise to do it
properly,
but this was like three years ago.
Two years ago.
It's not as not as big of a problem now,
as there's better governments.
But you know, I want to,
I'm thinking somehow end to end.
My end to end is different from your end
because you have a better perspective.
But I think all of these things is
relates to problem statement.
Problem statement at the end of the day,
is to make it self-serve for a firm user
to manage their users. Okay,
when you say manage users,
when they want to create or modify,
they can go through here, this UI,
and then take control of the user.
The permissions, everything today,
it's not possible,
because we don't give them the screen.
Yeah, I understand,
but let's say that if they have this
screen, they can do it by themselves,
yeah, of course,
because they don't know all the things
behind.
The all the resources behind this role,
they don't need to, we don't need to.
Our NCA team doesn't need to. OK,
so I think I get it now.
So we're talking about like kind of like
the solution, right?
We're at the solution level. Yeah,
our users, nobody sees this. Yeah,
it's just the implementation team.
We have to deal with this mess.
So that we can present them with a
feature list. Okay.
These are actually what Katy called, like,
these are all UI resource,
like UI module resources, right?
We just have to make sure we have a, okay,
if we want people to check off statements,
we make sure that's available in the
feature. Yeah. And then we show it,
and then that's all they see.
But what we're talking about is like any,
we all need to understand what resources
are and how they power the actual access
control because you might see things that
might not behave the way they're actually
done. So at the end of the day,
and that's why we spend so much time.
the UAR on the unified access request
form is because, like, fundamentally,
you can't you can kind of get away with
the sort of like, like, okay,
if you have a resource registry,
that's your feature registry.
You know what it is.
You just need to label some **** like a
feature.
Right? That's not a problem.
The bigger problem is in the way we do
packages,
which is why I want us to kind of
understand the packages.
As long as that feature registry or the
resource registry is there,
you can show people stuff. Like the UAR,
we can just pull it from the list, right?
And show people what they can select.
Well, at least what they have.
You can't show people what they select.
We'll kind of get into that.
So,
but as long as you have user kind of with
a user package within that package,
it's a list of resources.
I can actually then go in here because it
works today, right? Like, you know,
you look up, look up my profile.
I have a package, it's called manage all.
I go into the package and.
I see what's assigned to me.
I get all these modules.
That's not a problem.
I can technically give this format to a
firm. It just looks like crazy.
And I can't explain why you can select,
you know, statements,
but then you can't select something else.
That's why we're redoing the form. Right.
So this works. This is literally, I,
this form is.
Reading the user package that I have,
like the user package, and well,
and the configuration of the user package.
That makes sense. So,
with the new unified access management,
which the Figma, we go to the Figma,
we have...
more granular in terms of, for example,
icon opening, we show the underlying,
let's say, functions,
and also provide some buttons in terms of
control, manage, process, and view, which
is pretty much self-serve for the firm.
It is stored,
whoever that is going to control. OK. So,
so here's the problem, right?
So if we think about why we struggle to
put a form together.
Because this is the unified request form,
I can't believe we spent three months on
it. Uh, to replace my user access it, but,
but like, once you hear the story, like,
I'm like, OK, now I'm like,
this is not easy, so...
Packages, we're good.
Packages is a list of resources.
You need to have a user package to get
access to this.
Like you have to have a user package in
your user profile, right?
That's how you assign features.
A firm also has the same kind of concept,
but it's not for access control.
It's for me to define what the firm
actually has.
you have to marry the two to actually get
what a user gets, right? So what happens,
because as you can see here,
these package combinations,
like admin accounts and profiles, well,
if I assign a user with admin accounts
and profiles and it has the ability to
open accounts,
what happens if the firm opted out of
account opening?
I assigned you that package.
I can't change that package. It's fixed.
It's predefined.
You're going to get account opening.
So what do I do? Validation. No, yeah,
I have to validate, but against what?
Right?
I now have to validate against the firm
package.
So a user's permission and the feature
access is actually granted.
by taking an intersection of what's in
the user package and the firm package.
Whatever is in the middle,
that's what the firm,
that's what the user actually gets.
That's my life in the past five months.
I was going like that, right? So,
so this is,
and this is the other confusion.
That's why we don't show our firms this.
That's why we haven't given out
self-service.
We cannot allow any firms to understand
what user packages are.
We're not telling them this.
This is crazy, right?
Because then they're going to go, well,
I chose, you know,
manage accounts and servicing.
How come I don't see that for this person?
Well,
it's because it's not in your firm
package.
We didn't put it in your firm package.
You said you didn't want it, right?
But then the profile definition still
says I have servicing and orders and
account opening.
But we don't want to show that.
We just want to show what you're able to
select. So,
but then the only way to show what you're
able to select is if I pull up the firm
package.
Right, and I implement it on the form. OK,
and then the way I show what a user can
select is this is is based on that,
and to show what a user has,
I have to do firm plus user package to
show what they have.
Well,
firm intersected with user package to be
more mathematically specific. When,
when we when the vehicle comes from firm
360,
because it's there that they can define
services services they need, OK?
Well, so it's it will be there.
You're going to work on that with Ray.
But it's not right.
Of course it's not there, right? Ah, yeah,
okay.
Yeah, and I want to clarify,
we behind the scene or underneath,
we're not changing how we do the feature
management if we're doing feature
management and title management.
Just like the phone somehow,
because we cannot present.
the what we see on the user admin tool to
client for them to choose.
They don't know what the heck is manager
or manager order,
so they cannot choose by the user package.
And the way Owen is doing is to present
them the control they want to have.
So it is the same thing.
We're not simplifying the entitlement,
but we're trying to simplify or make it
more sense for the from the user access
request perspective. So they request,
they actually what they drive from the
form would determine the.
most appropriate user package to assign
to them.
So someone behind the scene will have to
come up with, if you choose, view here,
manage there.
It means you want to have the manage
service request package.
So we will do the translation behind the
scene,
but they will do the choices upfront.
So it's the same thing,
but then because we cannot present that
UI to client on the phone,
it doesn't make sense. If it makes sense,
we would have done that,
the self-serve user management long time
ago. But no one, even our internal teams,
they don't understand the user packages.
They just do whatever we tell them to do.
And that's how bad it is.
Yeah, we we have a matrix, yeah. Well,
technically, if you learn the matrix,
you'll understand what's what what has
what in it. It's, yeah, translating.
If someone want to manage account opening
and do whatever,
then we already have a matrix,
Radhika still did that.
to, is a macro,
so if you choose this and that on the my
request form,
it means assign the person this role and
then hire certain things, certain things.
So we already have a mechanism to do that.
So they don't come here and try to figure
out which user package to assign to the
person.
No one can do that. I cannot do that.
I have the JSON files. Yeah,
I also have all in search. Oh, okay.
So we can show the case. Okay.
So what are we doing now?
I guess it's time for a break.
I need a break.
Uprising.
Ohh.
This will save you.
And, um, so...
And he was in the shoulder.
This is very.
Can I do something?
Oh, Jason. She, okay. Or no.
Okay, show the day, so.
In.
You know your.
You'll get into this when we interview
you.
Yeah,
that's the nature of the legacy systems,
you know, yeah, this is not the, yeah,
this is not the screen,
but I'm sharing my screen in, yeah,
for sure.
Yeah, she's not on, so OK, on that. So,
you want me to, no, no, but I,
I'm sharing my screen on teams,
you see it, right? Yeah, yeah, I am. So,
this is the folder activation named Atesh
is working on,
so got all the user packages from
production.
And so, go in the latest one.
I sent you the link. I'm not sure, Graham,
you have access. I don't. OK, but I'll...
That's Penny versus.
Let me know if you have challenge. Oh,
I share. Yeah, I'll share.
Show of show from Q.
Again, so this is.
The one with all the disadvantages.
Mhm.
Also, like,
can you add me to this and BNI and
product team? Is that kosher? Yeah,
maybe that there already is there,
I think. I don't think so, no.
I send him a link here.
Anyway, so follow through this one,
the production JSON user packages,
the latest one,
and in here we copy all the JSON file in
here, and if we want to take a look.
One of them. This is the latest one.
It's called Global Men. Global Men.
Can you hear me? Okay.
Bing.
So, problem is our latest,
newest user package.
It has access to everything. So, yeah,
JSON file and then what do we expect here?
We got a title and mode is.
kind of the technical way how to, yeah, I,
yeah, maybe too detailed to explain it,
but anyway, you see resources,
so for each one of them,
we define a lot of resources in each user
package, and a lot of them.
duplicated.
So the same resources could be assigned
to multiple user packages.
And if you remember that,
That special if you manage orders,
like if you have access to orders, trace,
and you have the view control,
and then so certain resources will be
given if you have certain control,
and those controls are duplicated across
all the user.
Packages,
just like we have different permutation,
like one package may have will account
and then will order,
another package may have will account and
then manage order,
so slightly different and that
permutation is why is the reason why we
have so many.
different user packages,
but the resources are common.
So if you want to view orders,
so this one is view GIC manage menu.
So that would provide you the access to
click on the link and open up the GIC
application. So it's only that.
Whether you can launch the GIC
application is another story.
Here, it's interesting.
Resource ID 317 is View GIC Management,
and the bottom one is resource ID 3180.
OK, it's again GIC Management.
Yes, OK.
Yes, yeah,
both of them is ability to access, yeah,
or OK, uh,
what I don't understand is that.
When we say access,
it means that it shows up in the
navigation bar,
but if I don't have the view, yeah,
that's why I tried to hide from you by
not telling the access mode.
So now you notice,
so I have to explain it.
Yeah.
Yes, that's duplication.
And the reason is you remember on the UI,
we got the checkbox.
So you can check unchecked.
And if you uncheck,
like maybe someone by the user package,
as Penny said, by the user package,
you have access to ABC.
But then, for some reason,
your firm decided you shouldn't have
access to B. So,
when we set up your profile,
we will uncheck B. Yeah, so,
and how it how is it done behind the
scene is, again, I blame the architecture,
but...
It's every resource,
basically there's a duplicate.
So you have the mandatory resource type,
mandatory assignment,
and then the optional mode.
So if it's optional,
that means you have the capability to
uncheck it.
Something you don't see optional.
And that's intrinsic,
so you always must have it,
like the profile menu. You cannot opt out.
No one can say,
I don't want the profile menu capability.
But if something come with an optional,
is a duplicate.
But that means it will provide you the
capability to uncheck it.
And when it's unchecked,
so one of them will be assigned to your
profile and the other one will not be
assigned to your profile.
So then when we render the UI,
the system would know, yeah, you.
you should not see this one.
So it's an implementation issue,
not issue, but implementation details.
Yeah. So yeah,
that's why Owen kept saying the resources,
you have two resources and then you.
You have, we see the late restriction.
So if it's optional,
you have a choice to restrict access to
that and also restrict the UI visibility.
So that's about the implementation.
So that's why, yeah.
We, if you want,
for sure you can go in details up to
understand each one of them, but...
Yeah, that's a lot to...
to explain because even for the group.
They are they are grouped under GIC
management correctly,
so something you will see the type would
be different. Yeah,
this one and restriction for the bar the
top is false and for the for the I cannot
say for sure, but that like the idea,
that's why is duplicate.
But here you see the type of different,
this is a Jesse management,
and this one is a UI module.
So when you see CSUI module is always the
one to control the right,
the left hand side. Yeah, but, oh, sorry,
question. Assignment mode,
the only two capability,
the only two options are optional
mandatory.
two values over them? I think so.
And the assignment type, what is that?
Assignment type.
is.
I'm thinking.
Okay,
like if you don't know if it's all that's
fine. I don't know. Okay, no worries.
Yeah, and the default,
I'm not sure is in use. Yeah,
it makes sense a selection default,
but everything by default is checked,
so you cannot really see it.
But the pattern is the resource name.
We always named by, you know, view,
manage, or control something.
So this one is pretty standard.
If you see view equity borrowing order,
it means the capability to view it.
But it's not a good example because
equity,
we cannot control equity borrowing.
It's on the IIS tool.
But at least we have this convention.
that if we have view underline,
control underline,
it means that that function behind that
is control, for example, GIC. Mostly,
mostly because we we don't we don't
dictate that we like.
We don't provide the requirement how to
name the resource,
so it could pretty much based on the IT
interpretation,
and but I want to fast track or jump over
to this spreadsheet,
and because it's a more...
presentable way to look at the JSON.
It's still all the content coming from
the JSON files. And what they did is.
to flatten the file into the different
column.
So I think this would be a more
digestible way if you want to understand
the resources. So like if resource type,
each one of them mostly would mean the
application they are controlling.
So if we take a look at GIC.
Is just a good example. OK, so just see.
It, so first of all,
we see JSC is relevant to these four user
packages,
so it's not applicable to any other user
packages,
and if you cross-reference to the user
package spreadsheet, you will see...
None, not, yeah,
only these ones would have to manage,
yeah, Jesse, so, and then resource name,
I passed resource name should be over
here, so you see.
We only have the view GIC menu resource.
And the reason is JSC is an integrated
app. We can only control the app link.
So this is one of the integration tier.
So you click on it and then it open up
the app.
And then what you can do in the app is
controlled by your secursion profile.
Is there?
Either in this file or somewhere else, a..
.
a descriptor like, okay, it's applet,
it's whatever, like those kinds of things,
or do you have to just kind of know that?
You just have to know. Okay.
Well, the description is in the JSON,
right?
So like you see the resource description
is as far as it goes.
I don't know who gives them that
description because we don't.
I think they put it in the results.
I don't think we provide that. Who's they?
IT. OK. Firm and user management team.
Maybe Owen, maybe, maybe we can,
but your feature registry, does it?
This is spell the resource session? Yeah,
it's not like the integration type. Yes,
I, I don't let's not go there yet, though.
This is already very confusing, but yeah,
that might be something we're working on
a feature registry. Yeah, got it.
Okay.
So that has a column saying the
integration term. Remember,
nobody uses the resource description.
It's internal, right? No.
Like all of this, all of this is internal.
Yeah, that.
I just want to make sure that's.
Crystal clear. It's just for me,
I'm trying to think, okay,
how do you distinguish between that and
infinite or whatever? Yeah.
On.
We don't.
This level,
but we'll get to it because we're
actually introducing.
We just crossed.
So, so I mean,
so I want to take a step back because we
can go into the week one with this,
but basic concept do we understand, right?
So I want to maybe I'll do a recap. Okay,
I just realized I did an operational,
so I can maybe share this because this
would tie into...
Share my screen.
We're still recording, right? Yeah, OK.
back down. I need to,
we need to tie this together.
I'm a little confused as to whether
managing control are mutually exclusive.
They are not. Okay. Perfect.
They're incremental,
but can they be part of the same package?
Yeah, OK.
Yeah, if you, if you, if you're approver,
you're there's no reason why you wouldn't
open accounts as well. OK, yeah, OK. So,
to put us all back in context of the flow
and maybe to start to highlight the
underlying reason why we need to
introduce feature management,
feature registration as a concept is.
As you can see, when we onboard a feature,
what do we do?
We do a bunch of paperwork to make sure a
whole bunch of people understand what is
in this feature, what is this feature do,
what are the resources that need to be
defined by this feature.
And then immediately,
the only way we represent assignment of
that feature is we package it directly
into a firm package.
and we package it directly into one or
more user packages,
one or more firm packages or one more
user packages.
We throw all the resources in there,
as you saw in the global admin profile.
The firm packages look exactly the same,
right? So anytime we add a feature,
we have to do that. If we stop here,
then you go,
what are all the features in COPRESCOCHEF?
I wonder.
You can't get that from the system today.
Because the only representation of the
feature is if you look through all the
firm packages and you look through all
the user packages, right?
That's the only representation of feature,
right? So that's why we're like,
it's very confusing.
That's why we have registry,
that's a spreadsheet,
and then we have these mapping files of
features, the features, the packages,
the resources. So that's all,
there's a whole.
like bunch of people who have this
knowledge and that's what makes this work
today. However,
it does work in the sense of once you add
the features into the firm and the user
packages,
I can now go into and list what that firm
has and what that firm can be,
what I can assign to that firm, right?
Because as soon as I add the bunch of
resources into a firm package and I go to
manage firm.
I will now be able to say this firm is
using this package.
I'm now going to list what's in that
package here.
And that's what we see here. OK. Right.
So now I have that.
I can configure what the firm within the
default package if they want to fine tune.
Right, I can fine-tune that here.
Important concept to understand as well
is from an access perspective,
if it's in the package,
you have access to it.
You can choose not to use it,
but that doesn't mean you're ineligible
for it because we said,
if you have a core package,
you should actually have access to our
core services.
I don't care if your self-opening ID firm
that wants to use your own solution.
Technically,
you can still come back to our account
opening.
I'm not gonna block API access for that,
right?
I'm not gonna block feature access for
that.
Here is really just a place where I go,
I'm gonna show you what you have,
and then, you know,
if you really don't want your users,
if you really don't want any of your
users, right,
if you don't even wanna be able to
request for it.
Don't ask how this thing came to be.
We'll talk about that another day.
It makes no sense.
It's just time because it's internal,
so nobody cared. Really, yeah,
let's just dump stuff on there as we
added.
If I'm Industrial Alliance and I have my
own thing, right?
Industrial Alliance has an IP package.
They have an account opening.
in that package.
That's why it shows up on here.
But I'm just going to say maybe they
don't want any other users accessing it,
so I can hide it here at a firm level.
So it does not show up for anybody.
And it would actually,
I don't know if controls permissions,
Candi, right? It should,
then it would kind of prevent anybody,
even if like Industrial Alliance user,
or they moved over from hardware,
they found a URL, right? They can.
hack into it, they log in,
they found the URL,
technically they should, nope,
we blocked that access as well because
you need to validate against what the
firm package configuration is.
So loading the firm package, right,
adding the feature to the firm package
makes it show up here so that you can
further refine what users within the firm
can see.
And then adding it to the user package
means now I can assign a user a role that
is appropriate for.
Can you go back to the that you are? Yeah,
so in here you notice that the button is
kind of the module level.
So the show and high only apply on the
module level.
And then you see the check boxes below
the view, trade allocation, manage,
control process, everything.
So,
those are the resources under the trade
allocation or within the trade allocation
module, and they they are great,
so you cannot unselect or control it on
the individual results level,
but the control is only, I mean,
the shown height will only happen on the.
module level.
So that show you the hierarchy of the
resources.
So resources are under the modules.
So does hide mean that those...
Or.
Disabled as, yeah, yeah, you can say that,
OK.
Yeah, initially to the firm,
but like hide is the equivalent of
unchecking all of those,
but you can't check. OK, yeah, yeah,
so you won't see the um the module on
your for everyone in your firm.
These these check boxes should have never
been there, somebody just decided.
that actually if I built the user form
and I have the check boxes,
I'm just gonna use the same thing,
but then I'm gonna grade them out because
you can't actually select them. Yeah,
so this is a UI. Yeah, this is a, like,
so I wouldn't, like,
I think we can get into the nuances of
the capability gaps. This is a problem.
Like it was just hacked.
So it makes no sense.
But this is the design.
We want to show what you're unchecking.
This is not, no,
this is the incorrect orientation.
By the way, it's for our purpose in here,
we can see what are these resources.
And I think now you understand. Yeah,
so orders will have these resources,
right?
And then you can only control something
at the module level,
so then we can get into what module is,
because...
It's a very,
I feel like it's a very different
definition for the people you talk to.
But ultimately, yeah,
this is disabling the orders module at
the firm. We do that.
We don't allow firms to do it themselves.
Because again,
it has to come from a conversation
somewhere else on, hey,
what should you have access to?
What did you pay for?
And then it comes into Compass.
And then we assign the firm package so
that we show it here and then we go, okay,
what does the firm decide to opt out of?
Okay, I'm going to disable it for them.
Back into the to that diagram that you
were presenting here, yeah,
when we see feature onboarding plan, OK,
it means that, for example,
next week Stanley delivers a feature in
trading.
Okay, and roll out to the production.
So it means that he needs to broadcast to
us, to IT team, this feature, just us.
Just with us,
and actually it starts with product
activation,
because we handed off this whole
onboarding process to activation. Okay.
This feature is available and we need to
register that into our packages and so
forth. Okay. Yeah,
and actually you can see why.
And historically,
it's never worked out this way.
That's why we're talking to Graham now is
the onboarding plans.
never get defined until we're way into
development, but you can see the, like,
you can see that coupling of, well,
you gotta build it the right way first to
give me the right resources to control,
otherwise your apps don't work in the
ecosystem. So before people start coding,
we need to actually have that onboarding
conversation. Oh, okay.
Ideally, ideally.
Sometimes it doesn't work like that.
What was the latest one we did?
I think it was this.
So just to give you a flavor, right,
is you then kind of...
What?
I think I did this here.
This is the simplest one, simple one. Oh,
no, that's not right.
This is a very, very simple one. Actually,
I have no controls over it.
So maybe that's not a good example.
Let's see. So then we, we, you know,
product to product, we sit down and we,
it's product to platform, we go, okay,
what are you actually trying to onboard
here?
And so you have a conversation about
what's the feature, where does it belong?
So I know how to.
Group it.
Into the right capability bucket,
if it's a core, if it's not core,
we don't care, right? What's what,
what are you gonna make available?
What is the integration look like?
Is there any integration, right?
If it's if it's within Compass,
it's internal,
we don't really need to go into it 'cause
it's gonna adopt the model that we just
spoke about. If it's external though,
then we gotta negotiate. OK,
how much can we?
integrate, what tier, like, you know,
is that app going to manage the kind of
the fine grain feature,
like in data access management,
or are we going to,
are they going to take it from compass?
We have that conversation,
we document it here. Then we say,
where does it live? Right,
we have to have that conversation.
So then we know the UI resources are
defined in the right way and tucked into
the right modules as per Candi.
And then we also talk about the
navigation routing here,
and then we also talk about what does the
app need any context,
which is part of the integration
discussion.
If we need to pass language default and
it needs to register that,
we would define that in here.
And then we would get into skip data
integration because we never have that.
And then we would get into kind of like
the initial configuration of that feature.
just so that we know whether to show or
hide it for all the firms and show or
hide it for all the users when we start.
Based on this, then you actually create,
well, there's no, there's nothing here.
The problem.
All of them was ****** **.
I didn't do that one,
so I don't know how to speak to it.
I think maybe this is a better one.
I think I did this one.
So 4 features that have, you know,
that have controls that we need to
understand, okay, now I need to know,
okay,
who's supposed to get this thing at a
firm level?
So I define the firm packages that this
is eligible for.
And then I also talk about, well,
what kind of assignment do you have?
at the user level, right?
I know I have two resources here because
the feature does two things,
so we're going to have that conversation.
And then we're going to say,
do we want to show how to start?
And does this thing come with a view or
manage or control process? I don't know.
I'm a platform team.
I don't know what the hell you're doing,
right? So you got to tell me.
In this case,
CRS FACA is an account management app.
You don't need to know what it is,
but it's to submit some stuff.
So it has a managed capability.
So I need to have that conversation with
the PM to say, like,
that should be there somewhere.
And that lives under client life of
manager, which is account management.
So now I can map it to all the profiles.
Based based on that discussion,
so it's all in like a discussion is that,
that's why it's a dotted line box. Okay,
so under client lifecycle management,
FOPCRS,
these are all just like different feature
onboarding plans that we have, and okay,
this the IT team will take this and
they'll know what to do with it.
That, that's my problem, to be honest.
We say COPRESCOCHEF is not moderate,
is microservice. OK, this is why we claim.
So,
I understand that trading is a micro
service,
account opening is a account management
is a micro service and per micro service,
we have its product manager,
we have its underlying development team.
And we have a current platform,
which is COPRESCOCHEF,
that it has also its own features,
like user management, feature management,
and so forth.
Why we don't provide an SDK?
Or...
Cost, prioritization, time to market,
sophistication, engineering competency,
architecture competency,
product competency, all of the above.
You know, I mean, I mean,
from architecture point, I'm not,
it's not, I mean,
the architecture team when they built
microservice.
Yeah. Design.
I think they should think about
eliminating all these offline operations.
They never had the team to do it. Oh.
We don't have the competency.
We don't have a platform architect.
We didn't have one.
We had one architect that was a trading
architect and he got dragged into
platform management and platform security.
JP was onboarded a year and a bit ago.
Okay.
We never had a platform architecture.
Sorry, I didn't know that. Yeah, yeah,
there's no reason for any of this.
It was make do with what you have,
and then it got to this day until there's
maturity in the model and in the team.
And now you're able to kind of come in
and say,
look at all these things that are not
working efficiently. Right?
I think if you came in five years ago,
even if you asked for it,
nobody would know how to do it.
Because nobody understood our model,
nobody understood what should be on the
platform, nobody understood.
We actually were trying to build a
platform ecosystem. Nobody understood it.
It's a brand new team. I thought, yeah,
I thought that this structure that I see
today was well, sorry. No,
it was we actually, even just this alone,
I remember at the beginning when we were
trying to launch the platform, we spun.
The architect and Owen spun and the lead
dev 11 months. They were stuck on RBAC,
not RBAC, feature versus RBAC.
They argued about feature versus role for
11 months and we said, guys,
just put an end to it.
We'll just use it as it is.
And that's why it came to like.
Be like this,
and then we got rid of all these people.
Because we're like, we gotta move on.
Let's get a platform architect.
And even if we don't know,
then we can articulate it as well,
because at the time it was just,
we explained the model,
the business model, this has not changed.
It's all, even in old compass,
this is how it works. Yeah, right.
It was just not implemented in this way,
where we have a more kind of, you know,
like a more kind of concept around the
grouping of features and a product
hierarchy. The hierarchy wasn't there.
But the product hierarchy was there when
I started, right?
Like I just put it on a piece of paper
with Gray and then we just went for it,
right?
But the implementation wasn't there.
So now we're kind of...
duct tape, side bolt,
let's half implement this thing. Guys,
we're running out of time because we're
going to launch a whole bunch of stuff,
secure though necessarily coming.
So we just unmasked this problem and we
made it kind of bigger and bigger at some
point.
like where the inefficiencies become
unmanageable. Because I mean,
it sounds crazy, but guess what?
It actually works today.
So it kind of works.
Everybody kind of understands.
There's some confusion every now and
again, but not too much.
Would you go and change it?
Or would you do multi-firm?
We're going to do multi-frame because we
can layer multi-frame on top of this
model that we all understand.
And then when it becomes too inefficient,
right,
our ability to onboard features are slow,
our ability to expand the ecosystem is
too slow.
That's where you build the business case
to undo the mess. Actually,
You and the team has the page the way.
I think what it said earlier,
it's not saying the big problem because
already the platform has this enablement,
just we need to do something,
do in another way, but already.
paved the way and it's fine. Yeah,
it is like it has reached like the models
reach its limitations for sure,
but it also has reached a point of
maturity where everybody understands at
least. Well, it takes for like it takes,
it's impossible to onboard a new person,
right? Like you're just going,
what's going on? Like Graham is like,
what?
That means that there's the solution not
elegant enough, right,
for it to work effectively and for it to
scale effectively. However,
once you're on board, it kind of works.
So it has reached that point of maturity.
You know,
you're going to be looking at what is 1.
5 or 2.0 look like, right?
Is it still this or is it something
different?
Yeah,
and what's the what's the demand for it?
That's the most important part is we're a
business at the end of the day,
so decisions have to be economic.
If it kind of works,
then you we can afford 10 people to set
up freaking user IDs,
you're not auto-provisioning, right? Yeah.
Versus bringing in, you know,
bringing in the next system that's gonna
that's gonna allow us to effectively
upsell better.
I think the mandate also changed,
so before we only from a user management
and we got a different platform team to
take care of platform services and plug
in.
and so on. But then it will,
we combine the two and now we not just
onboarding or managing user.
Users,
but we're also managing the platform
relationship. So,
it should have been one team all along.
We just,
it was just too much work for one team.
Yeah, so kind of, yeah, evolve as well.
Yeah, yeah.
So,
but then to kind of maybe wrap this up.
Sorry. It's okay. No, no, it's good.
It's good observation.
It's A valid discussion. It is historical,
like every, like every legacy system,
which is just birthed out of something,
right?
So it's good to understand the reason
behind it.
Um...
Where are we? Firm settings, okay.
Don't worry too much about this.
I think we need to fix this at some point
too, to make it more understandable.
But same similar concept to adding,
so going through that paper process that
you saw and then the teams understanding
how to map it into firm and user packages,
we would do the feature mapping into the
user packages as well, so that we could.
as of any way today,
because this is what our internal team is
used to help provision users,
is we can populate this, right?
So then I know that I can select a thing
and then this package has this list of
resources in it.
Why some of them are checked off,
some of them are not. Then we just,
somebody decided to default with just
stuff against that package and.
That's why it is like this,
so don't worry about this as well.
That's a UI issue.
List of all these features. Yeah,
not package features. So, yeah, features,
technically resources,
technically a list of module resources
and optional resources. These are,
that's what these are.
But are these, can you,
can you uncheck these? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, that's the crazy part. Yes, you can.
Good.
And unchecking them means you don't see
it, right? What,
why do you say crazy work? It's fine.
Well,
it's 'cause this is check and uncheck,
but the firm settings you can't check and
uncheck, but it's the same component,
so ohh, okay. So, I like the first time,
like, that's why ohh,
because it it inherits from yeah,
that's why we had.
difficulty training product support
because it actually makes no sense.
Mm.
But it does if you spend time with it.
It kind of like it took me what Candi,
how long did it take me?
Like 2 months to figure that out?
Two months? Yeah. It's my whole life. No,
me, when you have to onboard me.
You're special, what they mean.
You're genius.
So, you started that, did you? You were,
I didn't some of those. I know,
I had no idea this is what you guys came
up with until Jason left,
and then I had to come talk to him. Ohh,
OK. This was two years ago,
and then it took, yeah,
it took me a few months to learn it,
'cause I was like, I think it did.
Breaking my brain. I know, yeah.
Wait a minute, which Jason is that?
Lipstead.
Okay.
Not necessary. Yeah, no,
I just didn't realize how long he'd been.
Yeah,
I've been I've been waiting for somebody
like him to come along for a very long
time.
I've been delivered for the past 11
months. Hey, that works two ways. Yes,
she did most of the work. OK, so,
so now we know,
right now we know we're up to here.
This is this is now the current state,
and then...
The UI module, obviously, like Candi said,
also goes to a, I don't know what,
I don't know what the actual physical
representation of it is,
but there is a platform UI thing
somewhere.
So then you can render the UI because
there's a, there's like, like Candi said,
there's a specific way the module are
organized.
And so that needs to be defined somewhere.
And then so there's a platform UI
registry, which takes then, okay,
what does the user actually have?
What's their configuration?
What's their assignment?
And I'm going to look up the.
This list,
and I'm only going to show the stuff that
is assigned to the user, and then...
Yeah, that's how you end up with. Yeah,
mostly deal with modules.
It only cares about modules.
That's how you end up with an app here.
Right. So that's.
feature assignment to people.
OK, that makes sense. OK, let's.
So yeah,
like to the extent that we can make sense
of it, that's where it is.
And then we can kind of go into,
so this side here is what we're now
adding for UEM. The problem is,
the problem is,
we really need a representation of
feature because we need to send
notifications.
We need to publish system health statuses.
We need to have not modules,
because modules are only things that show
up on the left hand nav.
They don't mean features.
They could be different definitions.
So we need definition of feature that's
not just a module,
so that we can show it on the form, right?
When user goes and...
Selects, where is it here?
When we built this form,
it's not built based on resources,
because that would be insane.
There would be too many,
and then we would have so much custom
logic to figure out to reverse engineer
the feature. Then we just kind of said,
well,
what if we just created a feature
management module? So.
You wouldn't need that data in F360.
Would F360 be the source of that?
This is a debate. I'm not sure. Okay.
Well, they need to be the same for sure.
Yeah. Right? But do you kind of go, okay,
I'm just going to assume certain things
about a firm in Firm 360,
so I don't have to have the full feature
inventory in there.
I think that would be the case.
And then which way you sync then would be
a question as well. Yeah,
I don't know yet.
That's part of the discovery. My biggest.
Concern.
with Firm 360 is the amount of stuff that
is now, it's not valid. Like it,
this is just, yeah, yeah, it's, we found,
we found a lot of issues, right,
when we first did the firm,
even the firm sync, right?
So Compass loads the firms from Firm 360
today, right? This list of firms.
Oops, I'm signed out, comes from Firm 360.
We found naming issues,
firms were complaining about how they
were represented. I think they were even,
I think they were mis-mappings.
I forgot what it was, Brad,
I can tell you the whole story.
Like this is, this is. We did an update,
like, our code's not always updated, yeah,
yes, like,
and then we sent the articles from there.
Yeah, so, like, when we first launched,
we saw a lot of issues.
They were like in data integrity issues,
and that is still the source, yes?
That still has to be the source. OK, yeah,
yeah, yeah, just I have to say,
they they consolidate all the family
information, right?
If it's in in camp or in...
In OSS or in Salesforce, yeah,
but those firms,
if they're not our plan yet,
they they exist in Salesforce,
we we don't care, so we only, yeah,
already active in Firm 360, yeah,
but the concept is Firm 360 would
consolidate all of those firms.
information so we don't have to challenge
our group pick up from somewhere else.
I've seen extensive procedures like done
in the last year now to get the data in.
What I'm not aware of is the maintenance
because like there's some,
who's owns that? It's still questionable.
Yeah, I'm not really sure. I'm not too.
I think Ray tries to figure it out and
then he kind of has to intervene. Yeah,
but like people that I think are assumed
to be the owner. Yeah, well.
Yeah, yeah, it's a it's a question.
That's why I think the when we talk about
kind of how much do you take from from
360, but first vice versa,
it that question has to be asked is like,
like where's the like,
is there like a data life cycle for this
stuff and who's doing it? If there isn't,
then I can't, because this is like...
To me, like Compass is the implementation,
is the access control.
You can't **** with this, right?
Otherwise,
you're going to expose firms on things
that they're not supposed to get access
to and users.
So if there is an integrity on this side,
then I'm going to say your configuration
point is Compass,
and then you get to report back what's in
Compass, right?
because at least this is completely
enforced and it's self-serve and it's
reportable, right?
And there's traceability and audit trail
and configuration.
So,
that would be how I would approach that,
right? Unless that's there,
then it's hard to it's hard to see what
people have done.
Is it like two or three years ago we have
that discussion with Ray and they they're
going to tighten up the maintenance and
the life cycle actually? Yeah,
so we we we were told to.
To trust the source of it? Yeah, well,
we don't we don't see the issues anymore.
Like I said,
like we just we we we found a lot of it
when we were doing the initial load of
the firms, because like we show this,
like that little box, right?
We show it to the firms,
like the firms log in, they see this,
they see their name of the firm,
and they're gonna go,
they they they kind of go, what, what,
like what, what?
My firm is not spelled like this. Yeah,
and also one key thing,
we load the firm range our codes from,
yeah, 360. If it's wrong,
it has a big issue. That's right, yeah.
So, like,
but that's still the conversation about,
like,
when you get when you guys get to the
feature.
Management is where do you where do you
take from and where do you report from?
The solution is in discussion, is not,
yeah, it's not, it's not complete. Yeah,
you need a solution that works.
Based on what people do.
So, oh, wait, we actually have it.
Oh, this is prod. OK,
I'm not touching that.
Where was I gonna go with this?
Here right now,
we add new features where this made-up
menu, yeah, so that so wait, wait,
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
this is, I don't know.
Why is it only accessible by you?
I guess so. It's in production.
I think it's in global admin. Yeah,
this is prod. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Where's my workflow?
I'm going to go back to it.
Where did I put it?
access management.
I was trying to operationalize the new
thing with Candi,
so I put a diagram in here. So, like I,
like I said before,
we you get up to this point,
that's how the platform works today.
We can assign firms with that,
we can assign with users with stuff,
no problem, right? It actually works.
I think there's like 9000 live users
using this thing for two years now,
and we're able to provision employees,
we're able to...
to provision clients, not a problem.
The only problem is, well,
how do you request for features?
How do you get, like, like you said,
notifications for features? Like,
we don't show, we often actually,
in the old, even in legacy compass,
your person,
if you're wanting this on the recording,
it's, sorry.
What am I? What am I sharing?
This is what I'm saying.
I'm seeing that. Oh, what? Yeah, no,
I have two tabs.
I have two Chrome into his open. Oh, okay.
There it is. Okay, thanks, Kris.
What was I going to say?
Was I talking about just now? oh my god,
sorry. What's your question again?
I asked that if feature right now we can
create the feature and we said, okay,
let's. So again,
this is like a matter of should you have
built kind of top down or bottom up?
Everything is bottom up. So at one point,
because we have to start getting out of
R2,
one of the things we do in the legacy
platform is we actually send outage
notifications.
to people which require an e-mail service
notification for and a representation of
the feature that has a notage.
We do that today, like this.
Why don't we see with eyeballs?
Of course we see,
so I pull back to my name profile,
my R2ID is tied to this one.
All of our firms have this problem,
they have to remember that.
In here today,
I think there's an incident,
so let's see if it showed up.
It didn't show up.
How do I make it show up, Candi? No,
it doesn't, it doesn't have,
it's not there.
I think yesterday it was like, yeah,
there was a, yeah, I was seeing, yeah,
yeah, yeah, I was seeing that. Okay,
perfect, yeah,
'cause we had an issue with,
I'm surprised 'cause it was an issue with
IMHOS today.
I think it's already resolved, I think.
Okay, so it's not there.
So you see the little bubble, right?
So behind the scenes,
and this is probably a better demo by
Candi because I'm missing a bunch of
stuff in my profile.
You can actually go and configure
messages against apps in the old compass
just to tell people that something's not
working.
And it's important because people only
come.
to Compass to do their administration.
They need to know if something's broken,
they can't do it,
they need to do it later, right?
So we need to publicize our outage
notifications through the platform.
This is old, remember,
we're trying to get the **** out,
remember day two.
So we need to move all of that into new
Compass. So Devindra,
who's responsible for the platform
experience right now,
started working on it.
And he created system health events,
which is this new module that we have in,
nope, wrong profile again. Sorry,
you remember it,
system health events where I can go in
and as an admin, I can go publish outages.
And then when I do, then I come to here,
then I'm going to get this little alert
thing that's going to show me system
health events.
in prod,
if there's any outages to any of the
applications. In order to do that, well,
what am I listing?
Am I listing the modules? Am I listing,
like, I have no concept of feature.
I need to introduce the concept of a
feature just to be able to use the system
health events.
That's how that thing came about. However,
that.
implementation with Vivek did not have a
conversation with JP platform architect,
which should have been a feature
management discussion. They didn't.
So it was just this like weird sidecar
thing that the system health events
talked to. So as of yesterday, I think,
right,
they finally had the conversation nine
months later.
And they said, guys,
feature management is part of platform
management.
It needs to be managed by you guys.
I can't have some other person.
It's already difficult to figure out
what's going on.
Devindra has no concept and should he
should never have a concept of these
resources to features to packages,
like none of that, right?
But I think that they do domain with the
problem is you want to publish.
events on features and only people with
access to that feature can see it.
This is an access issue.
This is a feature assignment issue.
So bring feature management back into the
conversation here. And by the way,
we're working on it anyway because we've
introduced feature configuration as part
of UAM. Okay.
So that thing should be replaced by
whatever you guys are working on now.
That's the long story for how it showed
up.
Okay,
and now the notification that pops up,
what's the detail of the notification?
I mean...
Because this integration right now
doesn't exist.
So what's the detail saying, for example,
order management doesn't work?
Something like that? Yeah, no,
like it's not accessible by users.
It's sitting there in the product doing
nothing.
Because it's just we can't use it because
like the feature management part doesn't
make any sense.
And there's old modules that haven't been
migrated into the new,
so we can't publish events for like, well,
what happens if there's an outage for a
feature in old compass? Well,
it's not a new compass.
We haven't registered that feature.
We have no representation of that feature.
Okay.
So now, really,
it doesn't send out emails,
doesn't also send out, no,
that's an e-mail service issue,
but it's also a prerequisite to launch,
yeah, it is,
but related to this specifically on
representing features,
that part is still missing, yeah,
and so we have to introduce.
a representation of features for all this
stuff to work properly.
Which is why, which is why.
You see that, well, okay, Penny, like,
I don't know, if you ask yourself day one,
you spent four weeks sitting in discovery
sessions,
why do we spend 4 weeks talking about
unified access request form?
Because technically you can just create a
hard code form and call it a day, right?
Well.
Well,
it's because if you want that form to
have context of what that firm has, right,
remember,
if the firm didn't want account opening,
why would it show up on the form?
It shouldn't show up on the form. Okay,
if we were to do that based on a current
model,
we're going to have to troll through the
packages.
right, to figure that out per firm,
per user. On top of that,
there are some things that are checkable,
uncheckable, right, that are, you know,
not very clear to a user.
So you need to represent that as
something that they actually understand.
For me to codify that,
I can't tell from the resource definition.
I have to translate it.
Right,
and then the the the check and uncheck,
especially when it comes to optional
resources,
you understand now a feature can have a
number of resources, a number of, okay,
how do I put them together?
The system doesn't know that at all.
You have to look into the packages,
and when you look into the packages,
resource, resource, resource, resource,
resource,
you can't tell that these are actually,
oh, that's GICs, right? You can't tell.
So we need to know,
otherwise none of the system,
like none of the apps that none of the
platform utilities will understand like
what the concept of features.
So what we said was, okay,
now we need to add a few things for that
form to work,
but also for any downstream things to
work.
right,
that relies on this definition of feature.
We said we need to add, first of all,
a system registry,
which is what systems are actually,
like what systems are actually available.
You saw that like in the UAR,
Graham doesn't need to know as much,
but we need to know that there's compass,
that there's secured zone,
that there is legacy. Within those,
then we need to understand, well,
what system, what.
features does that system have, right?
So we're going to now do a system
registry, we can create a system registry,
and then we're going to register all the
functions and resources that belong
within that system. From there,
now I can group those resources into
features.
So I'm going to create a feature registry,
right? So now I have a representation,
which by the way,
these are all manual steps still, right?
Somebody still needs to go in.
do it,
but at least I can now have a somewhere
in the database, like a definition,
a formal definition of this feature has,
yeah, exactly,
that's the formal definition, yeah,
of this feature has these five resources
in it, and these,
this is a UI resource and this is a
optional entitlement,
I can define all of that in there.
And so when I go and create the form,
the form is based on the features,
not the resources. I render based on the.
Yeah, when I go create the notifications,
the notification is based on the features,
not the resources, right?
System health status is based on the
features, not the resources,
because we can't be living off this
resource model forever.
Now we're taking the first step to get
away from it. The only problem is this,
obviously,
all of this still needs to stay intact.
So when you onboard a feature.
Ideally, you can see if we started here,
then what actually ends up being
populated in terms of features registry
is we should have been able to have the
ability to define the feature,
define the resources,
and then assign features to the user
packages,
assign features to the firm packages.
That's the only break now left in the
flow.
We still have to do this first so that
the assignment happens,
the role profile definition of that
happens, the firm assignment happens,
right?
But we also are going to do this so that
all this stuff that relies on a feature
definition actually has something to read
off of. Yeah, that makes sense.
That's the foundation and then over the
foundation. And then at some point.
All of this **** actually should move to
this side,
where you start from that definition, yes,
because you're onboarding the feature,
and then it flows into feature
association with packages, right?
But right now, there's no automation,
there's no auto population of these
resources, just like you know,
these people are physically adding like
the resources to the JSONs.
To automate it will take work,
it has to be worth it, right?
But that should have been the flow five
years ago. Yeah, I understand.
And as you said,
the left part right now stores in a JSON
file.
The JSON file is a source of fruit for
rendering the UI for any users who also,
yeah, yeah.
So,
it's combination of the JSON and then
base of the JSON,
it goes and map go to the OCTA and pass
the OK authenticates. OK,
not OCTA to JSON. Well, yeah, you can.
Well, now you have bases, you can.
Pull on the on the flows and get the
technical team to walk you through how
that works if you want. Yeah, for sure.
Cause I certainly can't explain it.
I've never looked that way.
I think this when you when I was checking
the API call with that to find out that
the template when you.
with the inspect on the Chrome,
you can see the sequence of the API calls.
So you can be demystified. It's good.
There's also a sequence diagram somewhere.
I've seen it before.
In our, in our work space, or yeah,
I think it's under NBN architecture or
something. Ohh, OK. Yeah, I don't,
I don't know, I don't,
I don't know where that space went,
so I didn't set to, yeah, I have seen,
I have seen actually JP is maintaining
that, I have seen that work space,
but I said the the best documentation is
under JP, yeah.
We are, we are the first. Okay.
That's great.
I think maybe we save platform
integrations for next Tuesday.
We'll have half an hour late.
I don't think we can get through it.
Oh, okay.
That's fine.
I just had a few questions about our
internal or internal processes about how
we maintain roadmap,
how we create features.
Candi provided me some information. Okay.
But I wanted to understand it, you know,
from top to bottom. Yeah,
we can go through that. We can, yeah,
I was gonna say that to the end,
but we can we can start that conversation
now, 'cause we can kick Graham out.
He doesn't need to be part of this,
but Graham, do you have any?
So TLDR,
we just need to put options into the
right packages. And then correspondingly,
because, actually, do we, yeah,
because Infinite doesn't own the
definition of what a user has,
we gotta give them the context as well.
So we gotta say, hey,
if you see this package,
this person should have options. Don't,
like,
if you see this person comes with another
package,
this other package doesn't have options,
so don't show them. Not by the package.
They chat results. They currently,
they have a way to get all the resources
by the user. So the user login,
got a token,
and then somehow you figure out the user
ID.
You come to campus and ask to fetch all
the resources belonging to this user and
then compare and maybe paper uploads
looking for paper upload resource and
then you load paper upload for them.
So is on resource,
not on the user package. Just, no, yeah,
and they also get the RO code.
So they have a way to fetch all the
Oracle, whether or not is a firm level.
Firm level is another flag.
So they know if this person is firm level,
they don't need the Oracle because they
own the cat RM. So they know. Yeah,
Ali sent me something on that. Okay. Yeah,
yeah. So they only know,
are you firm level? If not,
then I expect to fetch.
Your Oracle list,
and then that's how they control our data
resource. Ohh, sorry, data access.